<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Statistics on Bean Blog</title>
    <link>/categories/statistics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statistics on Bean Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/statistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide Mr.Bean</title>
      <link>/post/guide-mr-bean/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/guide-mr-bean/</guid>
      <description>div { text-align: justify; text-justify: inter-word; }  Mr.Bean
 Is a web application for simplifying the analysis of large-scale plant breeding experiments using spatial analysis , as implemented in the R-package SpATS . It provides the possibility for visualizing raw data, indentifying outliers, fitting mixed linear models (MLM) with or without spatial correction, retrieve  BLUPs/BLUEs and heritabilites from single-environment trials. Mr. Bean also provides a module for comparing multiple sources data (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outlier Detection in Spatial Model using SpATS</title>
      <link>/post/outlier-detection-in-spatial-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/outlier-detection-in-spatial-model/</guid>
      <description>ExampleRaw Data: Display of raw data in the field.Fitted Spatial Trend: Two-dimensional adjusted spatial trend without including the intercept.Fitted data: Fitted values of the model on the field.Genotypic BLUPs: The estimation of the random effects of the genotypes evaluated.Residuals: Display of errors on the field.Histogram: Distribution of BLUPs (Best Linear Unbiased Predictor).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>