<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Bean Blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Bean Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Model vs Classical Designs</title>
      <link>/post/spatial-model-vs-rcbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/spatial-model-vs-rcbd/</guid>
      <description>p {text-align: justify;text-justify: inter-word;}Comparación SpATS y RCBDUna duda que podría surgirnos en el momento de analizar nuestros ensayos de campo es qué tan bueno puede ser un modelo que tenga en cuenta componentes espaciales, frente a un diseño experimental tradicional como lo es un diseño alfa lattice o un diseño en bloques completos al azar (RCBD).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide Mr.Bean</title>
      <link>/post/guide-mr-bean/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/guide-mr-bean/</guid>
      <description>div { text-align: justify; text-justify: inter-word; }  
 
Mr.Bean  Is a web application for simplifying the analysis of large-scale plant breeding experiments using spatial analysis , as implemented in the R-package SpATS . It provides the possibility for visualizing raw data, indentifying outliers, fitting mixed linear models (MLM) with or without spatial correction, retrieve  BLUPs/BLUEs and heritabilites from single-environment trials. Mr. Bean also provides a module for comparing multiple sources data (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outlier Detection in Spatial Model using SpATS</title>
      <link>/post/outlier-detection-in-spatial-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/outlier-detection-in-spatial-model/</guid>
      <description>ExampleRaw Data: Display of raw data in the field.Fitted Spatial Trend: Two-dimensional adjusted spatial trend without including the intercept.Fitted data: Fitted values of the model on the field.Genotypic BLUPs: The estimation of the random effects of the genotypes evaluated.Residuals: Display of errors on the field.Histogram: Distribution of BLUPs (Best Linear Unbiased Predictor).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andean Bean</title>
      <link>/post/bean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bean/</guid>
      <description>--</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biothecnology</title>
      <link>/post/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/readme/</guid>
      <description> Team Final </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>